printcopy.info 2018-05-10

# Printers Copiers Servicing - Reference Manual. Pays, Privacy, Terms, Refunds policy

## Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions

### Privacy Billing Details

PrintCopy.info does not directly accept payments - we use an external payment processors to process all orders. Therefore, none of your personal payment information (ie. Credit Card number, bank account number, etc...) is ever stored on our website or in our database, nor do we ever have access to that data. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of PrintCopy.info.

### Exchanges

If you make a mistake and purchase a manual for the wrong model number/code, please contact us and we will gladly exchange it for the one you meant to request as long as the latter is significantly similar to the one you ordered and such document is available in our catalog.

### Refunds

Contact us, if you do not find the desired chapter in the purchased manual, or it was useless for you. We will refund your payment.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of PrintCopy.info.

###  Delivery methods

We use download as delivery method. You will receive a link to download the file immediately after payment. This link can be used many times within 7 days. If you need to download again after 7 days, contact us, we will update this link.

### External Sites:

PrintCopy.info is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

### Cookies:

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Service-Manual.net does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

### Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet:

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to PrintCopy.info and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through PrintCopy.info have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
